mergentonline.com 2015-05-26

# Mergent Online - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Mergent, Inc. and its affiliated sites respect and understand your privacy and your personal data. Mergent is committed to protecting your privacy so we hope that the following information will show we gather, use and protect your person data.

**Information Collected and Use**

Mergent collects information about our visitors, users and any other individual connecting to Mergent�™s sites in its day-to-day business. The information gathered and stored includes contact names, telephone numbers, fax numbers, addresses, email address, payment details and any other related data We collect personal data only through inquiries, registration or other voluntary means.

Personal information that we collect about you stays within Mergent, Inc., and any information distributed to third parties is reported in aggregate only. We do not give or sell your information to people who want to send you unwanted e-mail. We may however reserve the right to use your personal information to contact you about our products and services, which may interest you by mail, fax, email and (in certain limited circumstances) by telephone from time to time. If you do not want to participate, you have the right to ask us at any time not to contact you by ways of mail, fax and email.

**Cookies**

A "cookie" is a piece of software transferred to your Web browser. A cookie allows us to collect data about how our websites and services are being used and will not identify individual users. Mergent may use cookies to store some personal preferences for those visiting Mergent�™s site frequently. Mergent may place cookies on visitors' systems to deliver our service more efficiently.

**Credit Card Information**

Mergent offers some products and services via its website and visitors may purchase some of these products with the use of a credit card. The information contained in the credit card will be used only for transactional purchases and can be used only with the authorization of its owner. Mergent within fair and reasonable means will ensure that the credit card will be retained in our database and you will have the chance to change or delete the information at any time. You have the option of conducting your credit card transactions through an encrypted secured server.

**Changes to Mergent�™s Privacy Policy**

Mergent reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal data by sending a notice either in an email or by placing any changes on Mergent�™s sites.

**Questions and Suggestions**

If you have any questions or suggestions about Mergent�™s privacy and personal data protection policy, please feel free to contact us at [customerservice@mergent.com](mailto:customerservice@mergent.com).
